First Last

Operations Manager

Operations Manager with five years of experience in strengthening compliance, improving processes, and elevating output, quality, and customer satisfaction. Extensive knowledge of process optimization and data analysis.

San Francisco, CA 12345 +1 234 567-890 first.last@resumeworded.com linkedin.com/in/resumeworded

EXPERIENCE

Resume Worded, New York, NY

Operations Manager

January 2020 - Present

- Directed sales, call center, tool warranty and repair, billing, warehousing, shipping, and receiving activities.
- Reduced store's shrink by more than 25%, limiting operations loss and adding more than \$65,000 per year to operating profit margin.
- Implemented a system that streamlined the process by 10% and cut production time by 10%.
- Directly trained and managed 6 supervisors while leading a total staff of 55 team members.

Growthsi, Remote

Assistant Operations Manager

July 2016 - January 2020

- Increased sales within the first year by 15%.
- Maximized profits to the corporation by reducing waste in payroll administration by 5% weekly and increasing sales with up-selling strategies.
- Trained, hired, and supervised over 15 employees to meet company sales goals.

Resume Worded, Boston, MA

Production Technician

January 2012 - June 2016

- Implemented a system that streamlined the process by 15% and cut production time by 10%.
- Improved business efficiency by 20% by implementing broad knowledge in technical documents, computer and software processes, and knowledge of ISO 9001.
- Successfully developed and led a top-performing team of 10 in implementing production operations.

SKILLS

Project Management
Strategic Planning
Team Leadership
Customer Service
Negotiation
Business Strategy
Continuous Improvement

EDUCATION

Resume Worded University

Master of Business Management

January 2012

New York, NY

- Awards: Resume Worded Business Fellow (only 3 awarded to class), Dean's List 2012 (Top 5%)
- Completed one-year study abroad with Goethe University Frankfurt

OTHER

- Volunteer 15
 hours/month at the ABC
 foundation, leading
 pro-bono business
 projects
- PMP-certified (2020)